

# MARIA ELEONOR AURELIA

Flat 107 Snooker Point Bldg, Umm Hurair St. Dubai, UAE phone: (+971) 58 6204138 email: mariaeleonor0426@gmail.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Customer Service Representative (July 2018- January 2019) IBM Philippines Inc.

Laguna, Philippines

- Assist the technicians in coordinating with the customers and updating them regarding maintenance schedules or any issues.
- Resolve any service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint, determining the cause of the problem; explaining the best solutions to solve the problem; following up to ensure resolution.
- Keep records of customer interactions, process customer accounts and update actions taken in every service calls.

### Logistics Assistant

Chabros International Group

(Sept 2013 – Sept 2016) Jebel Ali, Dubai, UAE

- Coordinate with different departments to facilitate shipments.
- Create Invoices, Quotations, Packing List, Delivery Order and Certificate of Origin related to shipping duties.
- Arrange transportation, dispatch drivers to accomplish daily deliveries
- Communicate w/ vendors, customers to ensure timely delivery of goods
- Order office supplies and keep inventory of stocks.
- Prepare and send packages and important documents via couriers.
- Reconcile receipts and manage Petty Cash for the department.
- Handle telephone inquiries, sort incoming emails and faxes and provide general admin support.
- Create weekly and monthly status reports detailing department's operations and problems.

#### Data Encoder

(May 2012 – August 2012)

Santa Rosal Hospital & Medical Center

Laguna, Philippines

- Maintain database by entering new and updated customer and account information.
- Resolve individual transaction errors and report for any discrepancies.
- Perform other admin tasks like providing general support to visitors, handling telephone inquiries and emails, taking notes in meetings, monitoring office supplies and assisting in creating weekly reports.
- Ensure the office remains clean, sanitary and well-organized.

### **PROFILE**

Enthusiastic and dedicated individual with over 3 years experience in logistics and administrative processes. Expertise in providing admin support like filing, maintaining records, sending emails and handling customer complaints. A team- player who is recognized in providing excellent customer service

## **SKILLS**

Administrative Support	
Import and Export	
Documentation	
Data Entry	
Ms Office Proficiency	
Problem Solving	

## **EDUCATION**

Polytechnic University of the Philippines (June 2007- April 2012) **BS Clinical Psychology**